easyhomemeals.com 2016-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Easy Home Meals

## Privacy Policy

####  Overview

This web site is owned and operated by the National Frozen & Refrigerated Foods Association. We recognize the importance of privacy to you and the other users of the NFRA web site located at www.nfraweb.org (the "Web Site"). NFRA is providing this notice to explain our online information practices. This Privacy Policy applies only to the use and collection of data collected by this Web Site and does not apply to any other data collected by NFRA online or offline. NFRA may, from time to time in its sole discretion, change or modify this Privacy Policy and it will be effective upon posting of the revisions on the Web Site. By using this Web Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy.

As used in this Privacy Policy, "we" includes NFRA and any third-party vendors we hire to assist in the administration of the Web Site and/or the processing or handling of customer information. These vendors are required to maintain the confidentiality of the user information and are prohibited from using it for any purpose other than as described in this Privacy Policy.

####  Use by Children

This Web Site is neither directed to nor designed for use by any person under the age of eighteen without the direct supervision of a parent, teacher or adult.

####  Use of Information

We collect personally-identifying information that you affirmatively provide to us, including, without limitation, your first and last name, address, telephone number, date of birth and/or e-mail address. We use this information and share it with others as we deem necessary to provide you with NFRA’s services, including, without limitation, receiving NFRA announcements and newsletters, entry into various awards programs, promotional and sweepstakes offers, delivery of various marketing information by NFRA and/or its members, delivery and billing for products or services purchased via the Web Site, and, if you are a member of NFRA, for the publication of your personally-identifying information in the NFRA Membership Directory (which is available for sale on this Web Site). In addition, your personally-identifying information may be shared (i) as required by law, (ii) to protect and defend the rights of NFRA, the Web Site or the users of the Web Site, (iii) as incident to a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or similar event, (iv) under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of users of NFRA products and services, this Web Site or the public, (v) to complete any transaction initiated by you on this Web Site, or (vi) as is otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. The information you provide will be maintained for a commercially-reasonable time by NFRA for administrative, liability, and archival purposes. Comments, suggestions, or other communications sent by you to us are deemed to be non-confidential and we are free to use or distribute them in any way without compensation to the author, sender, or any other party.

We may use non-personally identifying information you provide to generate statistical information concerning Web Site use (for example, that there are over x number of users in a given state and that x% of the Web Site users are repeat customers). We may disclose this statistical information to third-parties. We may collect such statistical data by logging IP Addresses (unique identifying numbers that are automatically assigned to any computer connected to the Internet) and storing Cookies (text files that are stored on a web site user's computer by the web site) on your hard drive for system administration, security, statistical analysis, demographic analysis of Web Site use, and other such functions.

####  Links to Other World Wide Web Sites

We may provide, via the Web Site, links to other World Wide Web sites or resources and/or advertisements or other such promotional materials for third-parties, including its members. Because NFRA has no control over the content of linked-to web sites or the quality of the goods or services offered via these linked-to web sites, you acknowledge and agree that NFRA shall not be responsible or liable to you in any manner, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on the content of any linked-to web sites and/or the quality of any goods or services offered by or through any linked-to third-party web site.

####  Access or Correction of Your Personally Identifiable Information and Contacting Us

If you decide not to receive information from NFRA, simply opt-out by sending an e-mail containing your request to info@nfraweb.org. To request a copy of your personally identifiable information stored by NFRA, please send an e-mail containing your request to info@nfraweb.org. You must provide your full name, e-mail address and any other information reasonably requested by NFRA. You may then correct or delete such information using the procedures specified in the return e-mail message. If you have questions about this privacy policy, please e-mail us at info@nfraweb.org.

**National Frozen and Refrigerated Foods Association**  
4755 Linglestown Road, Suite 300  
Harrisburg, PA 17112  
Phone: 717-657-8601  
Fax: 717-657-9862  
Effective February 5, 2004
